<ModOps>

    <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002340</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Gate</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002341</GUID>
            <Text>Your journey into the world of man-made horror begins here. Be aware of trespassing ghosts!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002342</GUID>
            <Text>Large Halloween Tree</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002343</GUID>
            <Text>A crippled tree that is many hundreds of years old. A mysterious aura surrounds it after all members of an influential big industrialist family have met their deaths in the shadow of its crown.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002344</GUID>
            <Text>Dead Halloween Tree</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002345</GUID>
            <Text>Succumbing to the smog of the big city, these trees have been spookily decorated to make them at least somewhat respectable.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002346</GUID>
            <Text>Festive Halloween Tree</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002347</GUID>
            <Text>Some residents have taken on these trees to make them shine in the most beautiful splendour for the festival of horror.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002348</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Food Stall</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002349</GUID>
            <Text>Baked pumpkins, butterbeer and grilled sausages are distributed to hungry visitors here.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002350</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Sweets Stall</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002351</GUID>
            <Text>Candy canes, roasted almonds and pumpkin biscuits are distributed to the little visitors.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002352</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Cider Stall</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002353</GUID>
            <Text>The steam of hot cider hits your nose. A pinch of cinnamon gives it a special aroma. Don't drink too much or you won't find your way home!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002354</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Tables</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002355</GUID>
            <Text>Gather around and enjoy seasonal dishes delivered by vampire waitresses and zombie waiters. Sometimes a visitor throws his knife into the bark of the tree in the middle of the tables. This splatters red tree sap onto the surrounding guests.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002356</GUID>
            <Text>Spooky Halloween Well</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002357</GUID>
            <Text>One day a child fell into the well and was never found again. Since then, the water of the well is undrinkable and anyone who gets too close to it is overcome by a cold shiver.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002358</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Cauldron</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002359</GUID>
            <Text>Old witches dance around the cauldron, thick poison slowly bubbles away and foul-smelling vapours rise into the night sky. Stay back or you will become the next ingredient in the potion of the living dead.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002360</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Tree</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002361</GUID>
            <Text>An old gnarled tree decorated for the coming Halloween celebration.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002362</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Marketplace</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002363</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Marketplace</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002364</GUID>
            <Text>The pumpkin season has begun! After the harvest festival, the stalls are richly filled with autumn vegetables, decorations and plants. Ghostly red light spreads an air of mystery. Scarecrows in disguise give visitors a good scare, and tonight the biggest pumpkin in the country will be crowned.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002370</GUID>
            <Text>Halloween Ornaments</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1999002369</GUID>
            <Text>Spooky Ornamental Buildings</Text>
        </Text>
    </ModOp>

</ModOps>